(
"ai_sub_version": "3.4.0",
"generated_at": "2026-07-25T05:38:15.434535",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": false,
"max_retries_exceeded": true,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
※この配信は演出により激しく点滅する場面がございます 部屋を明るくし 画面から十分離れてご視聴ください
This stream contains flashing lights. Please view in a well-lit room and stay away from the screen.
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Come on in, welcome, welcome!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you so much! Thank you so much!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Come on in, welcome, welcome!
本日はお忙しい中、数ある配信の中から当配信、
Today, amidst your busy schedules, out of all streams available,
兎田ぺこら7周年ライブをご視聴いただき、誠にありがとうございます。
thank you so much for watching Usada Pekora's 7th Anniversary Live.
日頃のご愛顧にお答えいたしまして、兎田ぺこらオリジナルのステージを取り揃えましてのお出迎え。
As a token of our daily appreciation, we welcome you with an original Usada Pekora stage!
お祭り騒ぎでゲストもたくさんでお送りいたします！
We're bringing you a festive celebration with plenty of guests!
玉の方もメダルのほうもすべてチョーー、チョー、チョーー！
Both the balls and medals are super-duper-duper—!
お勧めでのお出迎えとなっておりますれば、どちらのお客さんも最後までジャンジャンバリバリとお楽しみくだされ！
Highly recommended, so we hope all our guests enjoy themselves right until the end!
日頃ご自慢の右腕左腕により一層の磨きをかけましてで、しっかりとガッチリとコメントもしてくださいませ！
Put your proud skills to work and please leave plenty of solid, enthusiastic comments too!
さあいらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Come on in, welcome, welcome, welcome!
ありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
Thank you very much! Thank you very much!
さあ、いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！いらっしゃいませ！
Now then, welcome! Welcome! Welcome!
本日もさまざまなグッズをご用意しております。
We have various goods prepared for you today as well.
ぜひ本日のライブの思い出に、おひとついかがでしょうか？
How about one to remember today's live?
ひとつめの目玉商品は、こちら！
The first featured item is this!
アクリルパネル！
Acrylic panel!
こちらはなんと、ホロライブEnglishのイナちゃんが描き下ろしてくれました！
This was drawn specially by Ina-chan from Hololive English!
とってもレア、とってもレア！
So rare, so rare!
そして、可愛いペコラをありがとうございます！ありがとうございます！
And thank you so much for the cute Pekora! Thank you very much!
イナ、ありがとう、イナ！
Ina, thank you, Ina!
是非とも皆さんのデスクの隣に置くと、いいペコですね！
It'll be so peko to put it right by your desk, everyone!
ふたつめは、こちら！
The second one is this!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Random acrylic keychain!
イラストは、ま丸絵先生に描いてもらいました！
The illustration was drawn by Marue-sensei!
めちゃめちゃ可愛いペコですね！
It's such a super cute peko!
是非とも全を揃えたくなってしまう、そんなランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Such a random acrylic keychain that you'll definitely want to collect all of them!
どれが来るかは、届いてからのお楽しみペコです！
Which one you get is a surprise waiting until it arrives!
みっつめは、ペコオーラ全開の「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ！
The third one is the "Uso Peko desho..." T-shirt, full of Peko aura!
この暑い夏を乗り切るのにぴったりなTシャツ、「うそぺこでしょ…」
A T-shirt perfect for surviving this hot summer, "Uso Peko desho..."
の場面がきっとある、そんなときにきたいTシャツペコですね！
There are bound to be moments like that, a T-shirt you'll want to wear at times like that!
よっつめは、トラックジャケット！
The fourth one is the track jacket!
こちらもまた最高にかっこいいペコですね！
This is also super cool peko!
後ろにはキービジュアルのペコラ！
On the back is Pekora from the key visual!
この中に「うそぺこでしょ」Tシャツ、そしてジャケットを羽織ってうちに行ったら最高ー！
Wearing the "Uso Peko desho" T-shirt inside and putting on the jacket to go out is the best!
お出かけにもちょうどいいペコですね！
It's also just right for going out!
そしてなんと、なんと！フルセットをご購入の方にはさらなる特典がございます！こちら！
And what's more, what's more! There are additional perks for those who purchase the full set! Here!
数量限定でペコラの直筆サイン＆箔押し複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる！
Comes with a postcard with Pekora's handwritten signature and foil-stamped duplicate message, in limited quantities!
以上、是非皆さまジャンジャンバリバリゲットしてください！
That's all, everyone, please get them like crazy!
兎田ペコラに夢と希望と未来を乗せまして、配信終了のお声がかかるまで一気にジャンジャンバリバリと最終最後のお時間までご視聴くださいませ！
Putting our dreams, hopes, and future into Usada Pekora, please enjoy watching all the way until the very final end, right up until the broadcast ends!
Ah 潮風に誘われて
Ah, invited by the sea breeze,
はしゃぐ声波の音
the sound of playful waves
近づいてゆく
drawing closer.
Ah 高い空 白い雲
Ah, high sky, white clouds,
まぶしい海と恋の季節
dazzling sea and season of love.
日に焼けた あなたが笑っていた
You, tanned by the sun, were smiling.
たくさんの光が キラキラ
Countless lights sparkling brightly.
コイする ココロで変わりだす ラッキー・テイ
With a loving heart, starting to change, lucky tei!
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our joined hands will cast a spell.
笑ってばかり ここは夏の国
Always smiling, this is the land of summer.
私をバージョンアップ！
Versioning myself up!
Ah 照らし出す 太陽が
Ah, the illuminating sun
まぶしくて かき氷 イチゴ選んで
is dazzling, choosing strawberry shaved ice.
Ah 青い空 白い砂
Ah, blue sky, white sand,
コントラストなピンクのくち
contrasting pink lips.
染まってく くちびる 照れ笑い 誘ってるみたいで ドキドキ
Lips turning stained, shyly smiling, making my heart flutter like it's inviting me.
コイする ココロがスピードあげてく
A loving heart accelerating its speed
恋するココロがスピード上げて
A heart in love accelerates its speed,
見つめるヒトミが 大胆になるよ
and the eyes that gaze become bold.
言葉はいらない 今を感じたい
I don't need words, I want to feel the present moment.
私をバージョンアップ！
Version up myself!
夕陽を映す海はオレンジ
The sea reflecting the setting sun is orange,
二人のシルエット
our two silhouettes.
足をさらう星の砂
The stardust sweeping our feet,
そっと、ねえ 連れてって遠くに
softly, hey, take me far away.
恋するココロは もう止まらない！
A heart in love can no longer be stopped!
合わせた手のひら 合図を送るよ
With our palms joined together, I send a signal.
何もいらない ふたりだけの国
I need nothing else, a country for just the two of us.
私をバージョンアップ！
Version up myself!
恋するココロで 変わりだす ラッキー・デイ
With a heart in love, a lucky day begins to change.
繋いだ手がほら 魔法にかかるよ
Look, our clasped hands are cast in magic.
笑ってばかり ここは夏の国
Laughing all the time, this is the summer land.
私をバージョンアップ！
Version up myself!
私のブランニュー・デイ！！！
My brand new day!!!
はーい、みな、ぺこらのライブに来てくれて、あ、りぺこでしたー！
Hi everyone, thanks for coming to Pekora's live, ah, thank you peko!
1曲目は、私バージョンアップでしたー！
The first song was "Version Up Myself!"!
1曲目当てた人いますか？
Is there anyone who guessed the first song?
何のね、曲が来るかみんなね、たくさん考えてくれたと思うけど、
You all probably thought a lot about what song would come,
まずは1曲目は私バージョンアップでした！
but first, the first song was "Version Up Myself!"!
ということで、今回も、うさだぺこら、パチンコスロットライブ第3弾！
And so, this time too, Usada Pekora's Pachinko Slot Live Part 3!
ということいで、おいおいぺこちゃん、
So, hey hey Pekora-chan,
前回も前々回もパチンコスロットライブだったじゃん！なんで3回目も選んだのよ！
the last time and the time before were also Pachinko Slot Lives! Why choose it a third time?!
て、思いましたよね？はい、私も、
you must have thought that, right? Yes, even I,
さすがにやりすぎか、さすがにやりすぎてるぺこなのかなって思ったんですけども、
thought, surely this is doing it too much, surely I'm overdoing it peko, but,
こちら見てください！
please look at this!
はい、「うさだぺこら7周年記念ライブ」ということで、
Yes, "Usada Pekora 7th Anniversary Live",
7なんです！7と言ったらやるしかないよね？そうぺこだよね？ということで、
it's 7! Speaking of 7, we have no choice but to do it, right? That's right, peko, right? And so,
今回もやらせてください！めちゃめちゃね、いい曲、たくさんあるぺこですので、絶対みんな楽しんでもらえる、
please let us do it this time too! There are so many great songs, peko, so I'm sure everyone will enjoy it,
それだけは自信があるぺこなのいで、
that's the only thing I'm confident about, peko, so
是非ともお楽しみに、そして、ハッシュタグのね、「うさだぺこら7周年記念ライブ」のたくさんつぶやいてください！
please look forward to it, and please tweet a lot with the hashtag "Usada Pekora 7th Anniversary Live"!
ということで、ここからはみんなお楽しみのゲストパート！
And so, from here on is everyone's favorite guest part!
今年はどんなお題が来るのか、お楽しみに！
Look forward to what kind of topic will come this year!
兎神拳に二対一の戦いはない！
There is no two-on-one fight in Rabbit God Fist!
覇王はこの拳をただ一人！
The Supreme ruler wields this fist alone!
北兎無双！
Northern Rabbit Musou!
何処まで往こうか ネイビーな夜空に映る過去の自分
How far should I go? My past self reflected in the navy night sky...
夢見がちだった 見たくないモノ 照らすハイビームに 走る焦燥感
I was so dreamy, illuminated by high beams on things I didn't want to see, rushing with anxiety.
跳ね除けて前へ往けば 信号は全色を無くし消えた
Shrugging it off and moving forward, the traffic lights lost all colors and vanished.
確かめたい この道が繋ぐ場所を
I want to make sure where this road leads...
深く、深く紺になる 夜を往ける この加速度
Going deeper and deeper into navy night, with this acceleration...
光さえ超えてゆける程に 強く、強く踏み込んで
Stamping down harder and harder, to surpass even light...
僕は駈ける ただ真っ直ぐに 譲れない想いを抱いて
I run straight ahead, holding feelings I cannot yield.
標識だらけの街を抜け出して 未来を探してた
Escaping the town full of road signs, I was searching for the future.
常識も何も 全部 雑踏と化してた
Conventional wisdom and everything else had turned into mere hustle and bustle.
何処まで往けるの なんて聞き飽いた台詞吐いて
Uttering lines I'm sick of hearing, like "How far can you go?"
曇った窓ガラスに書いた 本音 すぐに指で消した
I wrote my true feelings on the foggy window glass, and immediately erased them with my finger.
怯えても 揺ぎない軌跡 確かな願いを胸に 遥か遠く
Even in cowardice, an unshakable trail, keeping a definite wish in my heart, far away.
錆び付くように躓いても この真っ暗を 灯し進む
Even if I stumble as if rusting, I'll light up this pitch darkness and press on.
ただ一つ 答えを追いかけて 脆くても良い この腕で
Chasing just one answer, even if fragile, with these arms...
掴む為に 手を伸ばすよ 打ち鳴らす鼓動の限り
I reach out to grasp it, as long as my beating heart allows.
何度 この道で迷って 見失って どこへ往くの
How many times have I lost my way on this road, losing sight of where to go?
目指す場所も その意味も 一つしかないのに
Even though there's only one destination and one meaning...
曇った視界は 夜に溶けて もう一度 視線の先
My clouded vision melts into the night, once more ahead of my gaze...
僕を連れて往くよ きっと
It will surely lead me onward.
深く、深く紺になる 息を吸って今 加速を
Deeper and deeper into navy blue, inhaling now to accelerate...
傷付く程に強くなると 確かな色動き出す 纏ってゆけ
Getting stronger with every wound, a definite color starts to move. Wrap yourself in it!
迷い付けて 悪夢の果てまで
Straying on until the end of the nightmare...
一歩も引けない プライドから
From a pride that won't take even a single step back...
火花が飛び散る
Sparks fly all around.
まだ遠くても その手を伸ばして
Even if it's still far, extend your hand...
掴まえてよ Destiny star
And catch it, Destiny Star!
絆確かめ 未来の扉 開けて飛び立つ
Confirming our bond, opening the door to the future, taking flight!
輝くDestiny star 導かれて 希望の果てまで
Shining Destiny Star, guided to the end of hope...
譲れない想い 向き合う時 運命始まる
When facing feelings we can't yield, destiny begins!
数え切れない 悲しみを見つめ 光放つ
Staring at countless sorrows, a light shines forth...
Destiny star
数え切れない 悲しみを見つめ 光放つ
Staring at countless sorrows, emitting light...
Destiny star, Destiny star
ここまでじゃ、ぺこ助
That's as far as you go, Pekosuke!
恨みに歪んだ剣でペコーラは討てるペこよ！
With a sword warped by grudge, I can defeat Pekora!
紅い 雫滲む唇に
On lips stained with crimson droplets...
ふわり 嘆きの霧触れてゆく
Gently brushing past the fog of sighs...
空に浮かぶ鏡美しく 遥か暗夜の彼方照らしている
The mirror floating in the sky shines beautifully, illuminating the far side of the dark night.
降り注ぐ 数々の星に想い馳せて
Letting my thoughts race to the countless falling stars...
紅い雫滲む口唇に
Red drops soak into crimson lips,
ふわり嘆きの霧触れてゆく
A casual fog of sighs brushes against them.
強く、
Strongly,
強く強く結ぶ
Binding strongly, strongly.
瑠璃色に輝く
Those brightly shining azure eyes,
瑠璃色に輝く綺麗の瞳
闇よりの使いに閉ざされても
Though locked away by an agent of the dark,
繋いだ夢の橋誰も奪えないから
No one can take away this bridge of dreams.
無限の明日映して
Reflecting an endless tomorrow,
妖し光放つ鳴神に
Narukami shines with a bewitching light,
甘い言葉の蜜香り立つ
The sweet words give off the scent of honey.
密か黒い鼓翼忍び寄る
Secretly drawing near on black wings,
心臓鐘が
My heartbeat moans like a bell,
行き場求め呻き出す
Searching for its destination.
星霜の流れに隠す歪んだ罠
A warped trap hidden in the flow of time,
艶やかに鋭い牙を剥く
You reveal your beautiful, sharp fangs.
巡る巡る悲劇
This tragedy goes round and round,
玉響に消えゆく水泡のように
Like bubbles in the water,
儚い物語辿る運命なら
If it's my fate to follow this fleeting story,
曇りなき刀掲げ
I'll hold up the unclouded sword
清い詩紡ぐ
And spin a pure song.
譲れぬ未来のため
For this future which I won't surrender.
浅い眠り続く黎明に
The light sleep continues at dawn,
独り祈り込めて織り上げた
Woven by my solitary prayers.
涙青い雲に刻まれて
My tears carve into the blue clouds,
愛しあなたの影追いかける
I chase after your beloved shadow.
憎しみの炎渦巻くこの地上で
The fires of hatred that swirl on this earth,
汚れなき心貫いてく
Piercing through this pure heart.
熱き熱き誓い
A passionate, passionate pledge.
瑠璃色に輝く
Those brightly shining azure eyes,
瑠璃色に輝く綺麗の瞳
闇よりの使いに閉ざされても
Though locked away by an agent of the dark,
繋いだ夢の橋悠久に綴りゆく
This bridge of dreams will be endlessly patched up.
奏でる奇跡きっと…
By the melody of miracles...
可能性の兎
[Title: The Rabbit of Possibility]
未来ある若者の目を摘むな
Don't tie down the eyes of youth with a future,
後ろ向くなお前前だけ見てろ人生
Looking backward, living life looking only ahead.
ぺこちゃんのことが大好きです
I love Pekora-chan's way.
覚醒
[Awakening]
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
RE:I AM
時の鼓動がまだ響く間
Echo of a distant heartbeat.
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
時の鼓動がまだ響く間
時間の鼓動がまだ響く間
裸の言葉胸に閉じ込めた
記憶の色が滲み始める
破れた世界の隅で
何も求めずにただ抱き寄せる
今の僕にはそれしか出来ない
震えた強がりでもプライドに見える
逸れた子供のように
最後の声さえも
風がさまようせいで消された
月に手を向けたまま
君は空の星に消えた
「側にいて」と抱きしめても
もう2度と聞こえない君の歌声は
降り注いだ雨のサイレン
僕の代わりに今この空が泣き続ける
これまで踏みつけてきた教えを
今掻き集めこの胸に当てても
救い求め歌うような遊戯に見える
物語る大人のように
言葉に寄り添うだけの
空の愛と導きはいらない
飾られた祈りでは
明日の手掛かりに触れない
いつか君に届くはずの
名も無き幼い詩が描くわがままを
忘れたいよ一度だけ
眠れぬ悲しみがその詩を抱きしめてる
Freezing cold shatters my sorrow
And scorching sand puts it together again
投げ捨てられる正しさなら
消える事ない間違いの方が良い
臆病に隠してた声を今
この手で もう一度さらせば良い
掴む軌道も咲く光も
乾いた心のせいでモノクロに見えた
忘れないよ今日の景色を
ありふれた願いが足元を照らしてくれる
Please hear me
I want to tell you
Please sing to me
I wanna hear your voice
ふう…
Whew...
ぺこら一体どうなったぺこ…？
Pekora, what on earth happened, peko...?
一匹残らず…
Not a single one left...
食らってやる！
I'll devour you!
漆黒降臨
Descent of Pitch Black
Clawing inside my head
Shredding my self-control
It's getting close to the edge
I'm breaking down
Breakout
Fragmented memories are glitching in my head
Stuck in a moment and it's burning up
Bright red, a roaring howl disappears into the night
My soul is here to stay
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity
It's changing me, my heartbeat
Is racing so fast, unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now
I'm just getting started
Hey now
This ain't who I am
Obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now
Look what I've become
Obey now to me
Your hopes gonna turn to fear
When I scream
Corrosive voices laugh and whisper in my head
Tried to ignore 'em, but they're calling for a bloodshed
I'm like a puppet, someone's pulling all the strings
Drowning in misery, I can't get out
Breakout this rusted gate
Search and eradicate
Burning the hate from within
Ready to dominate
It's time to liberate
The chaos inside of him
Fading, I'm losing my grip of sanity
Straining me
My heartbeat is racing so fast, unleashing the carnage inside
Don't run away now
I'm just getting started
Hey now
This ain't who I am
Obey now
The voices confuse my mind
Let's go insane now
Look what I've become
Obey now to me
Your hopes gonna turn to fear
When I scream
ハラペコチャレンジ！
Harapeko Challenge!
負けないぺこ！
I won't lose, peko!
V獲得
Got the V!
ハラペコDRIVE
Harapeko DRIVE
伝説の朝に 誓った言葉
Sworn words in the legendary morning,
分かち合う声に 奇跡よ照らしせ
let miracles illuminate our shared voices.
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
風の舞うヒカリの空
The shining sky where the wind dances,
吹き抜ける残響
let's blow through the lingering echoes.
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
革命デュアリズム さあ始めよう
Revolution Dualism, let's begin!
以心伝心 生の咆哮 届いていますか?
Can you hear the silent uproar?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love is passed on.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of our dreams!
どんな人生だって
No matter what kind of life we lead,
いつかは交じり合う
we will someday cross paths.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
That day, you will pass judgement.
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
運命に委ね 流れのままに
Entrusted to the flow of fate,
変わらぬ明日じゃ 面白くない
an unchanging tomorrow isn't very fun.
沸騰せよ 血液のレイヴ
Boil up, raving of blood!
交錯する プラズマのように
Intersecting like plasma,
革命のデュアリズム さあ始めよう
the dualism of revolution, let's begin!
以心伝心 生の咆哮 届いていますか?
Can you hear the silent uproar?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love is passed on.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of our dreams!
どんな人生だって
No matter what kind of life we lead,
いつかは交じり合う
we will someday cross paths.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
That day, you will pass judgement.
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
Just trust my heart
Just feel my heart
...hold you
誇り高き愛の結晶
The crystalline symbol of proud love,
握りしめたら
when we clasp it tightly,
迎えにゆくから...
I'm coming to greet you...
刹那から 一生さえ
From this fleeting moment to a lifetime,
すべて見せて来た
I've shown you everything.
君へのLove song
A love song to you.
Break out! 鎖断ち切って 独立せよ
Break out! Sever the chains and be independent!
以心伝心 生の咆哮 届いていますか?
Can you hear the silent uproar?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love is passed on.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of our dreams!
どんな人生だって
No matter what kind of life we lead,
いつかは交じり合う
we will someday cross paths.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
That day, you will pass judgement.
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
Just trust my heart
Just feel my heart
...hold you
誇り高き愛の結晶
The crystalline symbol of proud love,
握りしめたら
when we clasp it tightly,
迎えにゆくから...
I'm coming to greet you...
刹那から 一生さえ
From this fleeting moment to a lifetime,
すべて見せて来た
I've shown you everything.
君へのLove song
A love song to you.
Break out! 鎖断ち切って 独立せよ
Break out! Sever the chains and be independent!
以心伝心 生の咆哮 届いていますか?
Can you hear the silent uproar?
化学反応 愛が伝承
Chemical reaction, love is passed on.
ついてこい 夢の果て
Follow me to the end of our dreams!
どんな人生だって
No matter what kind of life we lead,
いつかは交じり合う
we will someday cross paths.
その日 君はジャッジメントする
That day, you will pass judgement.
革命を Let's shout
Revolution, let's shout!
I have a big gun
I took it from my lord
Sick with justice
I just wanna feel you
I'm your angel
Only a ring away
You make me violate you
No matter who you are
It's all up to you
No one lives forever
Been burn in the hell
By all those pigs out there
Been burned in hell
It's always been hell
From when I was born
They make me violate them
No matter who they are
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
Have no prayer
So, I keep the gun with me
For my safety
I'll do it with no sweat
They mean business
No time for sissy pig
No time for sissy pigs
Queen of ocean
Sing "The Volga" to you
Queen of the ocean
No need to think about it
You do it or you die
Those aren't tears
Don't let it trick on you
Don't let them trick you
I am hard as steel
Get out of my way
Pay back all at once
Suck away the tender part
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
For Christ's sake, this rotten world
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon . . . I have it all
Weapon... I have it all
Get down on your knees
Get a good head on your shoulders
If it's for your guys
Go to the end of the earth
Do what you think
Give it with dedication
I'll put out your misery
You made a mess
For Christ sake, this rotten world
Shit out of luck
For Christ's sake, this rotten world
Go with my vision
Light up the fire
Right on the power
Weapon . . . I have it all
Weapon... I have it all
らん だむ ぶ れい ん ！
Ran-dom-brain!
わ おっ
Whoa!
叫ん じゃえ わ おっ
Shout it out, whoa!
事件 だ 毎日 タイヘン
It's an incident every day, what a pain!
大成功 の タネ だ と 笑え … 泣い ちゃうな 笑え ！
Laugh, saying it's the seed of success... Don't cry, laugh!
ぺ こらっ た るんるん らっ た
Pekora's skipping happily
ぺこら ん だむ しちゃいたいまえ
Pekorandom, want to do whatever you want
no no 脳 の 指令 無視 か yes か うりゃー
No no, ignore brain's orders, yes or uri-ah
no no 脳 の 指令 ランダム だ random ！！
No no, brain's orders are random, random!!
no no 脳 の 指令 無視 か yes か うりゃー 受取 拒否 れん ぞ ！
No no, ignore brain's orders, yes or uri-ah! You can't refuse delivery!
なんだ 意外 な touch and go
What an unexpected touch and go
びゅんと プロペラ まわれ
Propeller spinning fast
どこへ 向かう か は 知ら ない 知ら ない ん だ
Where we're headed, I don't know, I really don't know
なんだ 世界 は つなぐ ちゃう
What, the world is connecting
Error processing subtitles for this segment.
時代を彩るDreamer
Dreamers coloring the era,
無限の彼方へ
to the infinite beyond!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Ready, go!
乙女フェスティバル
Otome Festival
恋に焦がれてドキドキ
Heart pounding with yearning for love,
いじわるなんてイヤイヤ
teasing is a big no-no!
とびっきりのスマイルで あなたを連れてってあげる
With a dazzling smile, I'll take you away.
惹かれちゃうのは運命
Being drawn to each other is destiny!
あれもこれも抱きしめてあげる
I'll embrace all of it,
選ぶ道に誇りあれ
so take pride in the path you choose.
進めば 輝く未来
Move forward to a shining future!
乙女心 いつだってフェスティバル
A maiden's heart is always a festival,
きらめいて トキメキとどけたい 今すぐに
sparkling, wanting to deliver this excitement right now.
高く高く そびえ立つ壁も
Even towering, high walls
やがて超えてくイメージだけで Let's Go! Let's Go!
we'll eventually overcome with just that image—Let's Go! Let's Go!
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom,
一度きりの物語
in a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散りゆく運命だから
Because it's destined to scatter eventually,
やるだけやるんです
we'll give it our all!
笑いましょう 声高く 明日の自分に届けたい
Let's laugh aloud and high, wanting to reach our tomorrow selves.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって 時代を彩るDreamer
Yamato Nadeshiko, always dreamers coloring the era,
無限の彼方へ
to the infinite beyond!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Ready, go!
ワガママだっていいでしょ？
Being a little selfish is fine, right?
かわいいって言ってなでなで
Tell me I'm cute and pet my head!
お気に入りのスカートで
In my favorite skirt,
あなたに飛び込んでみたい
I want to leap right into your arms.
夢見るだけじゃ足りない
Just dreaming isn't enough!
決める時は迷わず行きましょう
When it's time to decide, let's go without hesitation.
その手で掴む時まで 未来へ加速して行こう
Until we grasp it with our own hands, let's accelerate toward the future!
Destiny いつか
Destiny, someday
あなたと一緒に
together with you,
永遠に触れてみたい ずっと憧れで♪
I want to touch eternity, always longing for it...
涙はらり こぼれ落ちる日も
Even on days when tears fall,
本気の愛で振り向かせたい
I want to turn your head with true love.
Going! Going!
花と舞い 夢と生き
Dancing with flowers, living with dreams,
重なり合う物語
in an intertwined story.
諦めなんて似合わないから
Giving up doesn't suit us,
やるしかないのでしょ？
so we have no choice but to do it!
期待から希望へと 願いを鳴り響かせて
Let our wishes echo from expectations into hope.
ヤマトナデシコきらめいて 高鳴りを越える Future Soldier
Yamato Nadeshiko, sparkling, a Future Soldier surpassing palpitations,
奇跡を信じて
believing in miracles!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Ready, go!
隠し切れない 熱い想いと
With feelings too hot to hide,
今を走れ走れ 負けない誓い一緒に掲げて行こう
run through the present, holding up an unbroken oath together!
あれやこれやと雅やかに舞うよ 予感に誘われ 情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
Dancing gracefully through this and that, invited by premonition, passion burns and takes flight!
無邪気なままじゃいられない 切り開いて見つけたいな
We can't stay innocent forever; we want to carve our way and find it.
本当の嘘もない私になって
Becoming someone with neither true nor false...
花が咲く 夢が咲く
Flowers bloom, dreams bloom,
一度きりの物語
in a once-in-a-lifetime story.
やがては散りゆく運命だから
Because it's destined to scatter eventually,
やるだけやるんです
we'll give it our all!
笑いましょう 声高く 明日の自分に届けたい
Let's laugh aloud and high, wanting to reach our tomorrow selves.
ヤマトナデシコいつだって 時代を彩るDreamer
Yamato Nadeshiko, always dreamers coloring the era,
無限の彼方へ
to the infinite beyond!
ご一緒に！ はいっ！
Together! Ready, go!
隠し切れない 熱い想いと
With feelings too hot to hide,
今を走れ走れ 負けない誓い一緒に掲げて行こう
run through the present, holding up an unbroken oath together!
あれやこれやと雅やかに舞うよ 予感に誘われ 情熱は燃えて羽ばたくの
Dancing gracefully through this and that, invited by premonition, passion burns and takes flight!
始まる歌
The song begins,
始まる鼓動
the heartbeat begins.
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
Let the sound of hope echo far and wide!
「生きる事を諦めない」と示せ
Show them that you "won't give up on living"!
熱き夢の幕開けを
The curtain rises on a passionate dream—
爆ぜろ この
burst forth into this
奇跡に嘘はない
miracle, without a single lie.
その手は何を掴む為にある？
What is that hand reaching out to grasp?
たぶん待つだけじゃ叶わない
Just waiting won't make it come true.
その手は何を守る為にある？
What is that hand striving to protect?
伝う熱は明日を輝かす種火に
The flowing warmth becomes a spark to make tomorrow shine.
さあ新時代へ銃爪を引こう
Now, let's pull the trigger toward a new era,
伝説の未来へとカウントダウン
counting down to a legendary future!
羽ばたきは一人じゃない
Our flight is not alone;
過去を越えた先に
past the obstacles,
創るべき歴史が咲き燃えてる
the history we must create is blooming and burning bright!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Binding our bonds and hearts as one,
響き鳴り渡れ希望の音
let the sound of hope echo far and wide!
「信ずる事を諦めない」と謳え
Sing out that you "won't give up on belief"!
可能性にゼロはない
There's no such thing as zero probability—
飛べよ この奇跡に光あれ
fly high, and let light shine upon this miracle!
切り裂けまだ見ぬ日に行く為に
Slash through to reach the days yet unseen;
不可能なことなんて一つもない
nothing at all is impossible!
こんなに心強いことはない
There's nothing more encouraging than this—
絶対絶対絶対信じ合いぶっちぎる
always believing in each other as we break through!
例え闇に飲み込まれてそうになって
Even if we look like we're being swallowed by darkness,
涙さえも血に濡れて苦しくても
and even if our very tears are stained with blood and agony,
帰る場所が待っている
a place to return to is waiting for us.
集え 守れ
Gather, protect,
誓え
and swear—
勇気の結晶が奇跡なんだ
the crystal of our courage is the true miracle!
願い、祈り、すべてを背負い
Carrying all our wishes and prayers on our backs,
本気を超える本気の謳
this is a song of earnestness surpassing earnestness itself.
痛みなんて何も怖くない
Pain is nothing to be afraid of—
爛れ 沸騰させよ
let our bodies seethe and boil,
このカラダ 羽ばたけ
spread your wings,
さあ 闇夜に 稲妻を
and bring lightning to the dark night!
出会い笑い合わせそして泣きじゃくり
Meeting, smiling together, and crying our eyes out,
命の炎も一緒に燃やして
burning the flames of our lives together.
五感の全部が叫ぶ愛と呼べるほどの
All five senses scream out, with an intensity worthy of being called love—
眩しく煌めいた友の証
the dazzling, radiant proof of our friendship!
絆、心、一つに束ね
Binding our bonds and hearts as one...
始まる歌 始まる鼓動
A song begins, a heartbeat begins,
響き渡り渡れ 希望の音
echoing far and wide, the sound of hope.
「生き事を諦めない」と 示せ
"Never give up on living," it shows.
熱き夢の 幕開けを 歌え
Raise the curtain on passionate dreams!
ゼロはない 飛べよ この奇跡に
Zero is not an option in this miracle!
光あれ
Let the light shine!
パマンドリゾートへようこそ!
Welcome to Pekoland!
わしわしわしわし わしがイク!
Wash, wash, wash...
トムハワードとは わしのことだ!
What's a Tom Howard? That's wash's business!
みんなライブを見てくれてありぺこん!
Everyone, thanks for watching! Aripeko!
このあと10時15分より
After this, from 10:15...
メンバーシップ限定アンコールLIVEが有るぺこーん!
member-limited encore live!
まだまだぺこーらも新衣装見たいぺこよね?
It's Pekora's new outfit!
ぺこらも歌も歌いたいしみんなに新衣装もっと見てほしい!
Pekora wants everyone to see more new outfits!
なので是非とも遊びに来てペコ!
So please come play, peko!
そしてグッズのおさらいです!
And now, the merchandise lineup!
一つ目はアクリルパネル!
First is the acrylic panel!
イラストは一那阿爾先生が描き下ろしてくれました!ありがとうー!
Thank you so much to Ina-n-chan for drawing this!
本当に可愛いぺこーらとかっこいいしおしゃれだし!
Pekora looks so cute and cool/stylish!
是非ともゲットしてみてねぺこな!
Please definitely get it, peko!
二つ目はこちら!
Second is this:
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー!
Random acrylic keyholder!
イラストはまろえり先生に描いてもらいました!
Illustrated by Maruiri-sensei!
いややっぱ最高のキーホルダー来ましたこちら!
This is seriously the best keyholder!
七やっぱ3つ揃えたいのがやっぱ人間の性なのかな?
Wanting three of everything is just human nature, peko.
どうぺこなんでしょうか?是非とも何が届くかお楽しみに!
I wonder what kind of peko we'll get! Please look forward to it!
そして3つ目は「うそぺこでしょ…」Tシャツ!
Third is the "Uso Peko de sho" T-shirt!
大人気の直筆Tシャツ「うそぺこでしょ」出ましたー!
The super popular "Uso Peko de sho" T-shirt is finally here!
部屋着にねぴったりだと思うぺこだけどもう…
It fits roomwear so well, but...
もううそぺこでしょTシャツで是非とも外に出かけるのも全然ありぺこだと思うので是非チェックしてみてください!
It's totally fine to wear outside, so please check it out!
そして4つ目はトラックジャケット!
Fourth is the track jacket!
KIBIZEROのぺこーらが着てるのと同じぺこ!
It's the exact same one Pekora is wearing in 3D!
是非ともぺこーらとお揃いで来ませんか?かっこいいしね、なんかおしゃれじゃない?
Don't you want to match with Pekora? It's so cool and stylish!
こちらもちまコンビニに行くときでもいいし、ま、それとも遊びに行くときでもいい、部屋着にしてもいい、もうねたくさん着てもらえたら嬉しいぺこなんで、よーチェックな!
Whether going to the convenience store or out to play or roomwear, wear it a lot and be happy! Check it out!
そしてこちらのグッズをフルセットでご購入いただきますと数量限定でぺこーらの直筆サイン&複製メッセージ入りポストカードがついてくる!是非ともお手にとってください!
If you buy the full set, you'll get a limited postcard with a handwritten signature and duplicated message! Grab yours!